>> Brian Holt: 所以我们没有修复另一个页面，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
we didn't fix the other page, right?
所以如果我们回到过去， >> Brian Holt: 我们可以
So if we went back over to,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We could just go ahead and
做得真快，细节比如，它还从语境里看，
do it really quick, in details such as,
cuz it's also reading from context and
上下文不再存在。
context no longer exists.
所以我们会把它删除。
So we would delete that.
我们将从连接中导入连接。
We would import connect, from connect.
对不起，不是来自连接，而是反应 - redux。
Sorry, not from connect, but react-redux.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
the context stuff down here,
我们会把所有这些东西都删除了
we would delete all of that stuff
cuz we don't need it anymore.
>> Brian Holt: 对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right?
我们不需要这些疯狂的东西
We don't need this crazy stuff.
这里的主题就是 props.theme。
And theme here is just
gonna be props.theme.
而道具，实际上，这将会是主题。
And props, well actually,
this is going to be this.props.theme.
>> Brian Holt: 我认为这是唯一的参考。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I think that's
the only reference to it.
好的
Okay, cool.
现在我们得把它连接起来
And now we just have to go connect it.
所以我们要在这里说
So here we're gonna say
const WrappedDetails
将等于连接(mapStateToProps) ，然后是 " 详细信息 " 。
is going to be equal to
connect(mapStateToProps) and then Details.
然后我们要把它改为 WrappedDetails
And then we're going to change
this to be WrappedDetails,
然后我们就得赶紧做正确的地图地图
and then we just have to quickly
right const mapStateToProps.
这就好了
That's gonna be this.
它将会以一个主题
It's going to take on a theme and
它将会返回一个主题在其中的对象。
it's going to return an object
that has theme in it.
>> Brian Holt: 对，因为我们的 redux 商店都有主题
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right, because our redux
store has both theme in it as well as
位置，但此特定组件不关心位置。
location, but this particular
component doesn't care about location.
所以我们不想注入这个，我们只是想注入一个主题。
So we don't want to inject that,
we just want to inject theme.
这就是为什么我们只有主题和注射
That's why we're only pulling
out theme and injecting that.
所以现在如果你再回去详细说明
And so now,
if you go back over to details, submit,
去看看胖子斯林
go look at Fat Boy Slim here.
还在读和写 redux ，对吧 ?
Still reading and
writing from redux, right?
所以我只向你展示的一切都是同步的，对吗 ?
So everything I've shown you so
far as purely synchronous, a redux, right?
我们没有执行任何 Ajax 请求。
We didn't do any Ajax requests.
我们什么都没做
We didn't do anything like that.
在这个过程中的 V3 或者之前
In V3 of the course,
as well as perhaps before,
我不记得我们之前是否做过这事我们过去
I don't remember if we did it before or
not, we go over redux thunk, which is
从 API 中获取内容的一种方法，将其返回，将其送入 redux。
one way to do request something from
an API, get it back, feed it into redux.
你能用雷达克斯完成更复杂的事情
Yeah, there's just more complex things
that you can accomplish with redux.
但现在我觉得这足以证明你是什么
But for now, I think this is enough of
a demonstration to show you what you're
如果你要重入重地的话就会变成这样
getting into if you if
you're getting into redux.
我们要把它重新设定好
We're gonna do git reset --HARD,
或者硬得像这样
or hard like that to HEAD.
然后我们就会
And then we're gonna
说 git clean -f.
say git clean -f.
我很难区分 mpm 和
I have a really hard time
distinguishing mpm and
它是三个字母的东西我经常用这两个字母
git cuz they're three letter things and
I use both of them constantly.
我想我得做 rf
I think I have to do rf.
没有吗
No?
>> Brian Holt: 好，随便吧。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: All right, whatever.
我想我还是有的，有的文件夹存在，但是
I think I still have, yeah,
some of these folders exist, but
我们去把他们手动删除吧
let's just go delete them manually.
服务器。
Server.
>> Brian Holt: 删除。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Delete.
>> Brian Holt: 和源。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And source.
>> Brian Holt: 到废纸篓，还原器，移至废纸篓。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: To trash,
reducers, move to trash.